examresultstips.com 2012-11-10

# Privacy Policy « Exam Results Tips

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while you are online at **[Exam Results Tips](http://www.examresultstips.com/)** ! We will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

**Email Address :** We will not share your email address with anyone.

**Log Files :** As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Links :** This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers :** We use third party advertising companies (Google Ads) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Copyright :** Linking to any page in this site is allowed and welcome, but hot linking to any other part of the content such as images is forbidden and illegal. Also downloading and using the content of this site other than for private usage is forbidden and illegal.

**Disclaimer :** All images and text contained in this Website were found on the Internet. If by anyhow any of them is offensive to you, please, [](http://www.examresultstips.com/contact-us/)[C](http://www.examresultstips.com/contact-us/)ontact Us asking for the removal. If you own Copyrights over any of them and do not agree with it being shown here, please send us an email with ownership proof. Please contact us with any legal problems and we’ll be happy to remove any thing in breach.

**Note :** If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, you can use this contact form to **[Contact Us](http://www.examresultstips.com/contact-us/)**.
